A good friend to meet, MBC
It's real, it's real
we are now
I saw 300 from where I was sitting.
I saw it
Come to your senses
Let’s celebrate annual leave this week.
You can have some lazy fun on the weekend.
what does that mean
we are lightning
Is it real money?
I have to go see if it's shit.
Let's go on a trip and take Jisong with us.
I made some money so I flexed
I'll shoot everything
Then I will buy food.
Let’s flex it properly
at this opportunity
Let’s make sure Jisong does the same.
Ah, then this trip is called
Someone else's trip with Munani
Oh, should I try it?
um
So this travel course is
I planned it all perfectly. What is it?
Let’s open the golden Namui
Yeah yeah
Departing from Busan Station and heading south
It's a course
When I like me
Over there across the sea
They say you can see all the small islands over there.
And above all
You can have an oyster experience.
2 kilos per person
I'm earning 3,000 won per week now.
I don't kill, I don't kill
Now and in the evening
Don't be surprised.
um
A dinner show is scheduled.
What a dinner dinner show
what's going on
Why is it not so good? Kim Ji-sung
you do it
I chose you as my travel guide this time.
Okay then
From now on
Very hot near Busan
Let’s start with the club. Club
I can't dance
This
Shouldn’t we start worrying about the Cookie Cup?
Why would you want to lose the cup? haha
You can learn how to dance.
Don't worry, just follow me
Now, to the rhythm like this
I entrust myself to you
While thinking, slightly wave
Let’s take a little gentle ride and see you, Han Seop.
Woo
completion
Ah, why are you so timid?
The dance is strong. Yes.
Ah Buddha greetings
Ah, Buddha greeting, Buddha greeting, greeting.
Buddha greetings
greetings
Why can't I
Ugh
Oh, why are you doing this?
으으
the door closes
I want food for my child.
us
It's a bit hard to eat just the two of us.
There are eyes that see
So with Eunsang unni
I called Jisongi.
If we were just on our own
Just between us, ignoring time and space
The problem is that it's fun
Is that so?
Ah, let’s go on a trip for two nights and three days.
I'm going to bury my bones there.
I'm going to play hard with all my heart.
Those bones are about to be buried in the club.
Fuze administration
Oh, that's just saying
There are a lot of places to go other than clubs.
I have to go to the mountains, I have to go to the sea too.
Um, where are you going?
I'm going hiking.
Now, Neungseong-gil Jumang has ended like that.
They said they gave it to me haha and they gave it to me at the club too.
You're a bit persistent
persistence
The door is closed
I really take control
Let's see, what's our relationship?
I feel like my heart has already been caught
At this point, Dahye Jeong
It's polite to listen to Mr.
Isn't it?
I don't know, Dahye Jeong's heart
Dr. Han is very helpful to me.
You are too much.
So we are friends
fifteenth floor
Why is the fifteenth floor
I have to go to the human resources department.
Attitude is bitter
As a deception, Da-Hye Jeong's place was destroyed.
Oh my gosh if you want to play
I guess I'm crazy
really wash it
What kind of deception am I
human mind
If you said you played with it, it's a deception.
That too far away
boss
suddenly
You are changing your position to the management side.
This
It's a labor-management conflict right now.
Dahye Jeong
What are you going to do with me?
As I said before, we are friends
Mmmmmmmmm so think about it
think about it
Try it and talk about it.
Why are you a parrot?
Why do you keep saying the same thing?
So
Jeong Do-hye is traveling now.
Thinking of going
excited and rational
I guess I can't decide
Come back and we'll be calm again
Let's talk slowly
Oh, let's see if you listened to the end.
Oh, okay, okay, I'll talk to you later.
Ah, first of all
After the trip, then
Let's talk again
The labor and management type is carefully
Hey, at first it doesn't even start
It didn't work well. Is this okay?
What
Thanks to you, my money was solid
Hey, I have to do this too.
Huh
Hey, look at the flowers over there.
Absolutely gambit ah
Oh, it's so good, sisters.
The jackpot went up again, 200,000 won
Okay Naiso
oh
Oh really, sisters
Ah, living in Seoul isn’t enough.
Come here and hear that damn coin
I have to do it again
no
This coin is on the rise right now.
I do it because I like it
You too, stop stretching and bouncing
Let's do it together
Oh, as soon as possible
You can make more money by joining
I said
again
If you say coin, you just go to Seoul.
I came down, down, down, down
Oh, okay, okay, okay, okay.
I won't say more
Ah so where do we start from?
First, let’s eat rice.
Now if you look here
where should i go today
I've laid out all the places to eat.
Yes, someone else's travel plan
Oh my my my my my
Hey, look at me organizing this.
uh
The kid who doesn’t do this even when working
So what are we eating?
I made a reservation because it was a good restaurant, but it was a bit expensive.
Should I wake up now?
Let's eat, let's eat.
Let’s spend our money properly
You came here to see
No, what
You need to know how to write
Because I know how to earn money haha, that’s right.
I lived my whole life just cherishing it.
It’s okay to have this kind of flex once in a while
In that sense
Let’s not go for the bluefin tuna course.
Oh yeah yeah
If you eat this, what's left
our fingers for two days
I need to suck it.
Even when you go, keep your mind
Don't let go and let's go
Haha I guess so haha definitely
Flatfish would be delicious too haha. I like it.
Then again
To the flatfish course
let's go
Ah
Wow ya haha
Um um um um
um
Um ultra long wave ultra long wave
um um um
Yeah
Um, try this too.
Yes boss
This is not natural information.
But we never ordered it.
Service
I like to see you eating well.
The best in our house
It's a menu
Give it a try
boss
Thank you so much. Thank you so much. Thank you so much.
Absolutely grateful, thank you, Berry, thank you, thank you
thanks
It's okay
Just a crazy bitch
Hehehe I don't bite uh hehehe
Thank you
kids eat kids
Thank you for playing like this yesterday
You didn't give me too much
Wow
hello
Mmm yum yum yum yum
um
Wow
Oh, I think he's stuck. Give me a toothpick.
This is this
Abalone Life
What a luxurious day it is
It's okay
Do you want to pick it with a toothpick?
Oh, I can't play with you because it's dirty.
It's really delicious
Oh, that's it.
Let's go to the car first
Jisung is in the bathroom at his house
Get some coins before you leave.
That's right, let's go, let's go
brother
Wait a minute
uh what
Did it fall a little? It fell.
Wow, the drop isn't that big.
Mistress, the reason it keeps falling like this is
Probably not
Oh no, wait a minute
Oh, that's strange.
Uh obviously
The flow was good
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
Ah, sister
When I told you to use a toothpick, it was dirty.
really what am i
I told you to stop yelling at me baby
It keeps happening
What did I do?
Oh, I've been saying no since before
Ah
Give me your hand
I won't watch it, yeah
Oh, I really won't watch it anymore.
no
I suddenly fell and saw it for a moment
Wait a minute
I don't see it
If it stays like this, the sisters will
Hit coins while riding
You can hit coins while climbing a mountain.
It's people
I blame myself for not really looking at it.
Okay, from now on, our Jisong
Do whatever you want
So give it to me
About me
This trip is my best with my sisters.
I want to do everything
That's what I really want to do
I'll just keep it until tonight.
Give me the phone, Mr.
Oh hey wait a minute
I don't give Dr. Han a sentence.
Okay, I'll give it to you.
So what should I do now?
What are you going to do?
From now on, we should really have fun.
Ah haha
I'll have some fun and see you.
Okay, can you get it? Let's see.
one two three
Like this
salty
Haha
um
I'm warm
When you come in, I want to search you from the waist down.
They seem like a starting dream team.
Hey haha
Oh, she's from Idol Star Athletics Championships
It's a generation, not a dream team.
Just haha
What is it?
Your expression is the stage of friendship
The montage is perfect
I'm a private looking for my mom.
stage of friendship
Oh, I'm annoyed, I understand, Mr. Lee.
Oh why
no
My mom also gets cupping often.
When I see you, I think of you
Oh, I kinda
spent a lot of money
On days when I want to
Strangely, it reminded me of my mom. Why?
For sneezing
Mom cupping every bone
floating
They say I can't rest as I go and it opens.
You are so foolish
I feel like I'm spending a lot of money
Oh I don't know
Every time I spend money
Secretly, I keep thinking of my mom
just play
All mothers feel the same
Something I've never done
I haven't been there
all the good things in the world
I want my daughter to enjoy everything
So, have fun and have fun
What every mother in the world wishes for
live as a daughter
Don't think about anything else
Ha, I see.
But you are speaking as a daughter.
I'm speaking as a mother.
I just
I'm speaking as a nerd, right?
Hey Kim Ji-song, let’s go drink more.
Why go play more?
Oh Jisong
But my sister's cell phone
Can't you just give it to me once?
I depend on my mom
I have something to say.
Uh oh I'm a famous person
I couldn't even check the text message.
mom it's me
Oh my daughter
cell phone
It's not lost
It all has its own circumstances.
rice
Oh, of course I ate it.
here
The rice is delicious and the sea is pretty.
I like people more than anything
No, tourists like us
Let me take a picture for you.
It's so sincere
Oh right
What kind of man was it earlier?
our legs
He said he would take a picture to make it look longer.
completely on the floor
I lied down and took a picture of it.
Haha ah
And the hospitality at the restaurant is really good.
Just keep providing the service.
A total abalone
So
Mom, let’s come together next time too.
Mom too
in an expensive hotel
Eat expensive food
Looking at the expensive scenery
Take a day off like that
There should be a day too
Yeah
I'm your daughter
My mom made a lot of money
I'll give you that kind of strength
mom crying
Ah
Wiping your mouth
Haha, I’m going to sleep so I’ll hang up haha
Mom, but what?
Maybe you don't get that kind of emotion?
Why are you swearing?
Wow
I can't give you my phone anymore, okay?
Why are you looking at me like that?
no
My older sister encouraged my mom to move forward.
You're shouting that you'll give it to me
Even though I know it’s just the actual captain
I'm a little jealous of your confidence
Ah, you too, do that to someone outside the country.
They say they make you like me
What should I do? Yeah
what am i
Three generations of chaebol hidden
It's not like she was a granddaughter, yeah.
There's no way
Coin yes
Oh really, sister
I am a promotional ambassador for Coin.
Why is it like this, who gets paid how much?
Not a chaebol or anything
people like us have
It's your only chance
life can get better
um
Just a pack would make things a little better.
I'll be picking up a lot of aloe packs later.
I'll upload it for you
aloe pack
Because of living
I probably didn't rent a shit car.
Where did you get that shit car?
What on earth did you do again?
Didn't you have money to rent?
kicking
To my cousin
What I wore was a surfboard
The waves are so nice now
Hehehehehe honey
The coming wave of implication
worry
Imple waves
What what
You're screaming like that with heat
You do it with heat.
Then hello to destruction
They say hello and take over your life
Ah, those sisters too today
I completely flexed it with heat and heat.
Why are you saying this to me Mr. Lee?
reflex
crystal
reflection super ultra black hole
reflection reflection reflection
Ah Mr.
Oh, I'm embarrassed
Oh hey, how can you do this when you’re five years old?
Is it the same as you?
Oh, I just look at you
The nagging feeling explodes like a sigh of relief
If it comes out, hurry up and sit down, sit down, sit down
Oh hey and the luxury you do
Sachi and I together
I know it's the same thing
together
luxury
Ah
What do you know huh?
I know this type of repair shop.
Sister, stop waking up.
uh
Oh, I mean
Hahahaha right
Hey, it's pretty good, look at it haha
Tteokbokki
Oh, don’t ask about the tteokbokki person.
Haha stop drinking
Please take one sheet each.
Now stop tonight
Roll it up
Woo
um
uh
Oh, what time is it?
sister
Jisong, wake up
Ah, I feel sick.
Wow
How many bottles did we drink yesterday?
Oh I don't know
Ji Ji-bae keeps drinking more.
So I did it because I felt unfair.
I can't even go to the club
You said there was a club with good water
When I found out, it was all suppressed.
And then oh
Oh, give me your phone now
Ugh, stay still.
Uh uh uh uh
Oh, I'm not here
Yeah
What, where did I put it?
There is no
I don't know
let me know
I tried calling all the numbers you gave.
three minutes
My phone is all turned off.
Ah Mr.
Ah
Uh oh
Sister, sister, sister, why why did something come out?
no
I even held it at the raw fish restaurant.
Then, in the cafe,
I paid
Oh no
child money
Because I use it everywhere,
There's no place to focus on
sister
Hey, I've been to a bar. What do you think?
There was no self-immolation or anything like that last night.
Lady, so
Why did you take away all your cell phones?
Did I know it would turn out like this?
Ah
Why why did something come to mind?
You got a text message from Dr. Han.
What is that about?
You're not in this serious moment right now
no my that
I came to Korea
I'm not saying this, but
Don't give it to me
Enter the mountain now
We have a set time
I have to leave.
I'll find my phone later
Why don't we just leave now?
Oh that's right
Because I said this
I'll contact the front desk.
Oh, I came this far, sister.
let's go let's go
No, I have to find my phone first.
No, let's go, just uh
Ah, Deoksusan Mountain
Flower viewing is not possible now.
I see it, sister.
Go ah quickly
let's go
go
Look at the weather forecast and see when it will rain.
Oh, we don't have cell phones.
What was the problem?
Should you listen to a song?
You go in and have a TV.
Ah, cell phone
Oh what was it?
radio
You can just listen to the radio haha
Better than today
No matter how much I saw it
Aha, what you like
Hehe, life is now
Uhhhhhh
Yes, I will go after listening to the advertisement.
This broadcast is from Kim Jin’s residence.
first place
It is being carried out with the support of Galbi.
Among the listeners who sent text messages
through lottery
I'm sending you some delicious ribs.
We ask for your participation.
After the table of coins
The rate of change is unusual.
Investors sleep well today.
You can't achieve it.
In that sense, this song
I'll listen and come back
Cho Seong-mo's regrets
Wait a minute, what is the DJ’s comment now?
Unusual fluctuation rate
No, I mean
I can't sleep because I like investors
It means sleeping
I'm so sad I can't sleep
No, why do I regret the song?
I'm saying I regret investing.
Or
I regret not investing.
Huh
Did you fall further?
Hey, check out the news.
Is there any news on this?
What do you watch news for?
Oh that's right
Then I called the broadcasting station and just
DJ's comment
If you ask me what it was
What do you use for your child's phone?
Well, Mr. Lee is a bitch.
Ah
Oh, what are you doing, sister?
What kind of flower viewing in Korea?
I have to go to a PC room
Let's go and see what's going on.
Something like a PC room is my one point mark
Because there isn't one
Ah, you just need to find your phone slowly.
What are you going to do if you take it slow?
Ah, quit the coin thing.
I think it's just a revelation from God.
just
God
You can't post anything to me.
I wonder if I apologize
Oh, what do you mean?
Now just turn the car around quickly, sister.
What are you saying, stay still?
Oh, stop it
I'm going to fight a little bit and I'm going to lose my mind, sister.
Ah
Oh, you don't drive properly
who says this
You suddenly popped out, you
You just said you to me, yeah
No, sister, sister, sister, let's just go
I'm going to have a real fight like this
Take out the car, Mr.
I have to go to the PC room now, sister, sister
stop stop
stop stop stop
Oh look at you crazy girl
Let's go, let's go
What is that cell phone just now?
Oh it's nothing
why is it here
cell phone
did you hide it
Actually
bar
I found it when I went
I was going to return it right away.
This is
Because I thought it would be
When I think about it, what
You girls always used cell phones.
cell phone
Because there is nothing, it is a really proper trip.
It was the same
If only I had a cell phone
You probably just kept playing coins.
Oh, so I said let’s do it together.
how much do we have with it now
Do you know if you're making a lot of money
Oh, that damn money too
Stop it, sisters.
so much money
How ugly it gets every time you spend money
I know you can see it
What is ugly
Hey Kim Ji-seong, I won’t say anything because you’re hiding your words.
What is it?
What am I wrong
I didn't even say it.
You're the one who's really ugly
What?
That's right
Dahye and I don’t have to use coins.
If you continue to work at the company
Even little by little
Salary is
I'm sure it will go up and someday I'll become an assistant manager.
I guess I can put it on hehe
I'm so jealous
But you
We are the assistant manager
Step by step while listening to the manager
When going up
What are you going to do alone?
I'm not interested in promotion.
I like it like this
yes
I also have that kind of pride
I like it like this
I'm not greedy for money
They might make a fuss, but
you know
You're not greedy
That there is no future
Sister, you know that too
Live only for today
Just like that, without any measures
It's not like I'm carrying it around
No matter how hard I try, there is no answer
I dreamed of a good tomorrow in the first place
Because you won’t be able to dream in the first place
It's afternoon
What
Why is Jisung coming?
know
There was
Oh wait, what does this mean?
Wait a minute, sister, since when did you know?
It's disgusting
I wish I knew everything
You pretended not to know and deceived me.
Oh it was really funny
what is this trip
What
I wanted to at least do it to myself.
Don't worry
I didn't use it enough to be suitable.
I'm worthless but I don't spend money
sister
I'm sorry
I
I didn't notice
I'm going to leave now
To someone who isn't worth it
Stop spending money
Have fun playing with two people
Ah, there is no Kim Ji-seong either.
Leave me alone
Oh my sister
Ah, why can’t I talk to you like that?
What are you very
I know you said it like silk
Oh wait a minute
First of all, I get it. Wait a minute, Jisung.
Jisung-ah
Yeah go go go
Are you the only ones going? I’m going too.
Oh really
I can't answer the phone, ah rain
Oh, it's really raining right now.
uh
Hey
Hey Jisong, hey Jisong, oh my
Oh wait wait wait wait wait wait
Wait a minute
Oh, that's real
ha
uh
hello
Oh my, where should I take you?
No, what is the car in front of there?
Ah, just then she disappeared again, lady.
guest to where
Ah
uh
Oh wait a minute uh
yes thanks
Deokjusan Mountain
Ah
Oh, I can't see anything.
Oh, take it, take it, ah
uh
Hey Kim Ji-seong
Why don't you answer the phone like this?
I don’t accept it because I’m not intelligent.
Oh sister
Jisung Kim and I changed cell phones.
I made a similar crazy key ring
Ah
But you don’t answer the phone like that?
Oh I don't know
I'm on Mt. Parkju now.
If you have any conscience, come quickly
My conscience is in the Middle East
It's been a long time since I went to work
In that house
When we meet, use a cell phone
Bring it with you
Oh hello hello
Ah, Kang Yunseong
Lady, why did you leave the car behind?
You're dragging me all the way to Seoul.
What is it
Oh really
Eww
Ah
Hey Kim Ji-seong, where are you?
How come I don’t do it right away?
Oh, oh, it's noisy
Because I’m in Deoksusan right now
Come out right away
The trip is going to be so crazy
It's not a trip, it's my heart being broken
Come on, it will be difficult.
Hey, it's a hiking trail and you covered it.
I came here after seeing that
I'm sorry
This is Eunseong
I can't talk for long because I'm on a phone.
I've been on the phone for a long time
If I use it, what else will I find fault with?
I only have one oil.
Hey IC
Oh my, these are the real ones
Oh, what should I do, where are I going?
Ah
Ah ah ah
Oh crazy
Ah
Ah ah
Hello
Oh what is it
Why don't you reply to my texts?
Oh right
I was shocked
I can't see the security guard right now.
I couldn’t believe it, I went to the mountain ah ah
It's really a mountain right now
Please save me
again
Ah
Still
Wow, it’s refreshing to me
Wow it’s cool
It really came out, Jisung, don’t cry
But the phone call
It keeps disconnecting
Ah, this is Eunsang’s phone.
I guess Yugeun also uses the cheapest one.
There isn't much data
We need to use up a lot of data and break off relations.
We don't play together
I am sister sister
Because I follow it well
Inside, I thought the world was at ease.
now
Even if the company sees me, I’ll pretend not to notice.
Don't play then
What if I quit my job?
Let's quit
Quit and come hang out with me
It'll be fun
What should we do to see each other again in the spring?
uh
no
It's nice to hang out with you.
If you quit the company
Where is the money for flower viewing?
Maybe you
No need to rely on labor income
It means there is asset income.
You know, I did it yesterday too.
Now is the era of high inflation and low growth.
The 10,000 won we saved this year
Jang next year
For 5,000 won
It might not even be worth it
What does it mean?
Like this now
If you live sparingly,
Oh, why are you like this?
I bought a watch
uh
Did you see it? Jisondo Together
Our Couple Watch Together
Together Gaeko is Together
Ah, honey, it's an impalation that's coming
I'm not scared of the waves
Jisung-ah, don’t lie, nag me
What nagging
Always remove new items
in shoes
What kind of money are you using in your wallet?
In the future, in the world
I know how things will change and I spend money like that.
Are you writing a lot?
When I just look at you
Anbansu
The nagging is coming out like an explosion.
ha
It was this
The nagging explodes like a sigh of relief
To come out
I have to cherish you a lot
Dahye Jeong
I was going to die like this
What are you doing?
Make sure you save money every month.
Mr. Dong-gu
Come to your senses
Team leader, you can’t die in a place like this.
Stay alert
Why is the team leader worried about me?
Ah, this is a dream, Dongwoo.
If you die, I will take over from the company.
There is no one, Dahye
Mr.
Dahye, come to your senses.
You can't die here.
Mr. Dahye
No matter how poor Da-hye's life is,
Even without anything
construction window
Even if it's the same, you should never give up
Oh, is it Mac?
Sorry, Dahye, there was no baby.
It was clear just now
It seemed like the baby was full.
Uh uh, you can't fall asleep.
No more
At this moment Dahye
The person you really want to see
What do you think of that person?
Wouldn't it be better?
The person I want to see is Dahye Jeong.
what is this
Now until Dr. Han’s year
I'm hurt
can you wake up
no
Let's piggyback
Ah
Mistress
Kang Hyun-sang’s conscience
I came back too early from the vibrations.
Ah
Where is the time in this?
I don't even answer the phone
uh
No, it's strange, why are you calling?
Hello, Ji-seong Kim.
Oh, it's not Kim Ji-seong.
It's not Ji-seong Kim's call.
Oh, it's true that Kim Ji-sung called.
Oh, what are you saying?
I'm saying it's true, I'm saying it's not
Oh, I'm so busy.
Tell me, I'll tell you
Oh, sure
This month's accounting written by Ji-seong Kim
ask where the chart is
Please give me a corporation
card usage statement
Ask your team leader if he has forwarded it to you.
Would you please give it to me?
Because the team leader is on vacation today
Oh, they haven't even used open recruitment yet.
Without packing up the car
I can't do it
What the heck, take care of that cheap one
As soon as they knew who I was and called me
Why are you slurping and cursing?
I put a rose knife in my mouth
Oh look
no and
Is only Team Leader Baekri on vacation?
Jisung Kim is on vacation too
Annual leave is for employees.
What are you calling about?
Give it to me
Give it to me, I learned it from him.
Oh my, look at what this person is saying.
Who is this kid?
Who are you?
Kim Ji-seong is Mr. Amiol.
What are you doing now?
Oh, this trip is really great.
Haha
Is this a pervert or something like this?
Let's face it
People say it's the best haha
It's real
Jisong and Eunsang
I'm feeling a little worn down from the fight.
Still
Overall, everything was good.
But now
Even the dream is so amazing
It's a dream
I just have to be in Seoul like this.
It's right in front of your eyes
If this isn't a dream, what is?
Oh, I have to wake up quickly.
what kind of child
Oh but wait a minute
If it’s a dream, why do I have to wake up?
I'm Dahye Jeong
Even in my dreams
Am I the wrong person?
Baby, it's not like that.
Otherwise, what is it?
As I travel through my mouth
I learned the fun of spending money.
How much does it cost to spend generously without sparing anything?
Is it fun?
I figured it out
Still
I feel sorry for Dr. Han.
yes
What about Dr. Han?
These days, I really, really
It's a dream I cherish.
Thoughts too
It's such a waste that sometimes
I really take it out little by little. Hmm.
If you get too excited all at once
I'm afraid it's bad for my health
Hmm
I guess I'm excited
Of course
Because
you are so damn handsome
It's funny
Ah
Oh no
I have to wake up now. Really, wait a minute.
Wait a minute
Wait a minute, Da-hye, lower your neck.
Neck. Neck.
Mr. Da-hye, neck, neck, Da-hye
Mr. Neck
Ah ah ah my tailbone ah ah
Oh what
This is a dream, why am I hurting too?
Dr. Han
This is real
Ah
Huh
Oh, you're crazy
It's me who's crazy
Not Assistant Manager Jo
Now my sister
with my cell phone
You were promoted to Manager Cho.
no why is it my fault
original vacation
Work related to the employee who killed him.
You shouldn't call me
Why is that so unreasonable?
I'm coming
What if you come
Oh, it's an indefinite contract job.
That's completely different from regular employees.
It's something else.
The same goes for the salary increase rate.
Even during holidays
My sisters are like that during the holidays
I received a gift certificate worth 50,000 won.
That was grumbling.
Are you like me?
I can't even get that
Ah, the situation is like this.
A phone call like that while on vacation
I got it
Like my sister, I do it all like this
Can you hit me?
Hey, if you're in that situation
Even more
Shouldn’t I try coins?
Oh really that
Oh why why why
Well, what about that damn coin?
Oh well, they said they would at least invite me to a chat room.
I don't care
When you make money
Invite to that chat room
Be it or not
I don't care
Your life is beyond that room
bigger and
Because it will unfold in a shining place
funny
The thing that shines is his eyes that are outside his eyes.
The number that shines when you smile
That's what Auburn teeth are like.
Hey, do you like being handsome that much?
Being good-looking is just a temporary thing
No matter how much he is
Without thinking
Even though he is a pathetic squire, he
world class handsome man
A pervert who found it difficult in a rich inheritance
It's mine
Oh, steakflation
Even if you make a mess, you can't save it
He’s as handsome as Diamond
you
you you bitch
You studied
It's on my side
No.
Wow Mr.
I am now transferring to school
three hundred, etc.
While doing it, two hundred and ninety-nine
In terms of grades, she’s a bitch.
I think I see it
Jang Han-nyeon
Jang Han-nyeon ha
Don't come
don't come
Jang Han-nyeon, don’t come, oh, don’t come.
Uh uh uh
uh
Ah ah
Ah ah hold on tight
Ah
Oh, sister, let go.
Hey, if it were you, would you let go?
Oh we got it too
Wow, this is our tusk.
Ah
On days like this we both fall
sister
Ah
Sorry, uh
What kind of picture is that again?
Hey, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly
quickly
quickly quickly quickly quickly quickly
quickly quickly quickly quickly
quickly quickly quickly
Ah
Ah ah ah ah
Ah ah
What is it
Ah hey
original travelogue
Was it going to be this spectacular?
So, from next time, what you said
Let's take the train anyway
Safe dinner show
I saw it, but I
How did you hit your head when you fell?
I guess it's okay
Now it looks like it's peeled off
This is Dr. Han.
No, not until I came to visit.
I guess it contains my boss haha. Why?
I have all these nightmares
Haha, it's okay. Why are you like that?
I really tried to talk to you again.
Then are you okay? Yes.
I even thought it was a dream
sleep sleep sleep sleep sleep
Stop being surprised now
You know we practiced
It'll be up soon
uh
It's up and it's up
What's wrong? Wake up. Let's do it quickly.
Hey, you know that
We did that back then
What I practiced back then
sit next to it
You know, sit together, sit together, sit together
Paste it uh uh uh
Let's sit together and sleep, sleep, sleep
sit together
Oh no
Oh, sister, you've come to your senses. It's okay.
Oh what is it
Oh what happened?
ha
child
I was injured, but Jisung was the one who fell.
Why did you faint?
I passed out uh
that
The rescuers said that from the helicopter.
With that cochlea
The person responsible for breaststroke sensation
What is the vestibular organ?
They say that's what happens when you're weak
I suddenly fainted
To put it simply
So
why did i faint
It's like that because you're old, lady.
You were worried.
I thought I was going to die
I'm going to die
me me me me me
Ah ah
Everything you said is right.
I have no answers from one to ten.
the right thing in my life
There is nothing
no suddenly what
Hey and what else
Why did I say that much?
So
That's why I didn't like coins.
I only have sisters
Those kind of sisters
You keep leaving me alone
I feel like I'm flying
No, I mean
I'm asking you to do the same.
I'm scared
What
my life
coin-like
Even if it’s a trend like that
So much so that I have to hang on
Admitting that I'm broken
That's scary.
I'm trying not to ruin it.
I'm not doing it because I'm broke.
my life is ruined
I said I ruined it, but why are you like that?
I'm ruined, but I'm in ruins.
How much is the card worth this month?
I know you do it
Well, because of the surfboard
Hey, what did you do when you bought that one?
that so
Suitable for surfboards
I also bought a rash guard.
Buy a pair of shoes
One hat too
I also have a bag
This isn't just one, why do I keep doing this?
Are you saying it's one?
When I came to my senses
I also made a reservation for Gwangppa Inkido.
Oh my
That fact
I was in the sauna for three days.
Uhhhh uhuhuh
Dahye, uh
I need to take some more medicine
let me sleep
Otherwise, I will be in a bad mood.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, okay?
Okay, sister, sister, sister
Who would spend that much money?
Why did I nag you so much?
I don't want to hear it
That's right, that's right, that's right, it's clean, that's right
Hey, please support this
Be really quiet.
uh
Sister uh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
Hey you really
Are you doing the same thing with a five-year-old?
Since yesterday
Who are you treating like five years old?
You, Kim Ji-seong, you, uh
Ah
I
Kim Ji-seong, a five-year-old who looks just like you
I know one
Should I tell Kim about my beloved Tao?
um
He is
The child had just turned five years old.
For a while
It was when I started learning Hangul.
He said he couldn't even write his own name well.
There had to be one letter wrong.
So the name is
The child on earth
One day, I became Ji-seung.
Another day
Jisong also became
Uh, since when
Our name was Jisong
From now on
I should call Ji Sang Ji Ji Song.
uh
When you can write your name correctly
I guess they promised to go to the amusement park.
Dad bites the truck
Mom was busy cooking meat on the grill.
with my child
Because I didn't have much time to do it
That other kid
If only I could write my name properly
With mom and dad
I thought we'd be together this year
Oh, even though it came out thirty minutes ago, this is it
It's so blocked
uh
Wednesday ah
Wednesday is
Because it was a day when my father was working, I
I have to take care of my child.
Not on Friday, yeah
Ji Sang-ah
It's dangerous, sit up straight, it's dangerous
Ji Sang-ah, sit up straight.
Oh no no no
Uh uh see you that day then
money
I wish I could find something right at the right time.
So sometimes
That kid got his name right
On days when I feel bitter
The poor parents were heartbroken.
These letters
The pairing is a bit out of date
It sticks out, yeah
This is not a square
It looks a bit like a circle, yes.
From then on, I used it well for no reason.
In the handwriting he wrote
I heard they found a fault
They say that sometimes the child just whimpered in his sleep.
We're pairing up
I just baked one pair incorrectly.
how
time
Let me see
That's how I want it.
On a day like that
Like today
It rains so much
It was the day to come
That kid
Breathe on the window
Blow your name
I mean, it was written down.
Jisang Kim
Not a single letter is wrong
Again and again
finally
So then the amusement park is
It would have been fine if I had just left it the way it was.
no
I couldn't go
Why
Bury the child in the ground and come back
I was in the car
Ah
It was an accident
daycare center
The bus received a guardrail so it only took time.
If only there were more
praise him
There must have been moments
If only I had more money
The better he can be slow
moments
There must have been a lot
Those moments that can't be returned
His mother, whom he regretted for a long time,
I lived because I couldn't die
They say we met again one day like a miracle
two pairs
I didn't fail
Pairs not yet completed
It wasn't drawn wrong
Although I'm clumsy
very slowly
One line that is carefully drawn
So Kim Ji-song
What's wrong with you?
You don't even wear clothes
Whatever you want, whatever you want
I can do it
It's still being made
To call you a failure like that
It's not too early yet
yes
Tell me
I don't want to fail yet
sister
It's me
yet
I have no idea what a coin is
Kang Eun-sang, I want to trust you and give it a go.
I am also someone who believes in me
I'll trust you and go.
I also want to coin
Why
No way
The train has already left
You install the app first
If I create an account
Five of my coins in your account
I'll send you ten
If you put this in money
It's about 8.7 million won
no that much
You can give it to me like this, it’s not a waste.
What's the waste?
This is Sachin together.
um
me too
I also shoot five
Not 8.7 million won
87 million won
No, let’s go until it sounds absurd.
Let's go to the moon, yeah
Let’s go to the moon haha. Let’s grab each other’s shoulders.
What is it haha
Ah, that's what I thought
Let's go, let's go
It was like that tomorrow
What I want
When it happens, the first thought is that
did
Do I need that now?
The answer was always the same
A little more later
a little later and easiest
save
Because the only thing that could do it was my heart
Let's not do that anymore
With these overflowing good people
Let's be happy without any evil
we have enough
These people are worth it
Ignoring your space
They have fun among themselves
Byung
Ah
uh uh
Hmm
Maybe it's because it's been a while since I went to work
It's a little awkward
Hmm
It's not awkward being with me
Are you upset? Of course.
Why did you wake me up?
Let's be friends
Heung
Oh my
Oh wait a minute
no
This is an elevator.
I have to make that absurd expression
Not that way.
I didn't ask you to be friends
Huh
I did it
But
Why are you criticizing me for being friends?
Then no
Dr. Han
I understand that you are more than capable of meeting me.
I knew it, uh
tell me how many times
Oh, that's right
Please don't stop talking. What is it, mecoter?
Dr. Han
You are truly a very talented person.
He's cool and talented
Still, I want to go.
With Dr. Han
I don't want a man as a friend
We started as friends
No matter what realization comes
once
Stick around
No matter what trouble you face
Like an exciting adventure
Let's have fun
us
together
Yeah
I like it, I like it, what?
Whether it's a transition or something, it's an adventure.
If I work with Dahye Jeong,
Everything is good
Well, I'm asking something so obvious.
Oh right
But that day, my boyfriend
How did you come here?
yes
So
Why did we come all the way to Namhae?
changjiang travel
What are those famous musicians?
While working
When I get stuck, I just leave for an unfamiliar place.
of this world
I wrote famous songs, so
what approach
I don't think the method is bad
Okay
Instead, it goes until Friday.
I have to go to my part-time job
You too
Because of something important at work
That Vietnamese branch love
Is it an engagement ceremony or a contract ceremony?
Oh, of course I'll go until then.
It's an important position.
Wow
uh
Oh my, oh my, you did that
I did it like that
No, it has to be like this
Because my legs are long
thank you
Ah thank you
Thank you and take care.
Still expensive and delicious
Welcome to the right place
What more should I give you?
Then shall we give you some more shrimp?
Uh ah, this house is everything
Hey, yeah
Does the golden pear ring in a place like this? Yes.
I am now
Abalone on the table before this
I want to shoot
I just ended up lying on the floor.
Haha
Good I am
There isn't one, hey.
hello
No, that
I just want to ask you something.
Yes, do you know any clubs?
This seems like a nice club.
No, there's no club, there's a club
It went out of business
So hurry up and go
Why are you so angry?
Oh, it's funny, really.
I live hard, I work hard
Please save me
Mr. Dahye Dahye
Mr. Oh, I’m surprised.
What is it
What are you doing
Hey what
Where are you going now?
We are not going to Seoul
I know it's dangerous
Just leave it alone
Hey, you're not going to the convention room.
It's too late to leave now
You're not going to Seoul right now.
You're the one who's really in danger
What kind of owner are you really?
Not even my son
Such an important thing
Do you want to save your place by ruining it?
uh
What is he
They say it’s Baekje
no hey
Hey Hamju
Oh, this isn't crazy, really.
How did you come to this place?
I have no intention of telling you that.
Let's make a promise
What promise?
Slowly starting with friends
Well, it’s good up to that point.
What should I do to not be too frugal?
Just my thoughts
In the future
Don't be generous, just be generous.
'Cause I'm already doing that
Hmm
yes
ha
Wow
what is this
Well, is there something interesting? I don’t know.
This is not good
I don't think you'll find it fun.
What is it
the door is open
Here we go
why are those people
I keep mulling over it.
Is it because of that incident?
Tell me it's true, Shingoyo
Does it matter?
No matter how different the positions are,
Jinho Kim, pay me from now on.
Each one is big
I'll take all the money
It keeps falling
The coin ran out
additional number of copies
For no reason the time has come
I'm not suffering
Because salary alone is not enough.
What is this, Mr. Goi haha?
They keep an eye on their shit.
I already protected it from Team Leader Go.
If it gets to the point of sweating like this,
Really Wow
If you get caught, you'll die.